Macbeth Gallery Scrapbooks
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Scrapbooks, 1892-1952, Series 5:; (Box 120-130; 3.3 linear feet)
  - Scrapbook 20, 1949-1952 (Reel NMC4, Frame 332-400)
Nov. 10-Dec. 6, 1919 Third Exhibition of Intimate Paintings (NMc2: 512-518)
Dec. 10-31, 1919 Loan Exhibition of Paintings by Emil Carlsen (NMc2: 520-527)
Dec. 3-20, 1919 Paintings by William Baxter Closson (NMc2: 520)
Jan. 9-31, 1920 Thirty Paintings by Thirty Artists (NMc2: 531-536)
Feb. 2-21, 1920 Paintings by Charles H. Davis, Frederick C. Frieseke, Richard E. Miller (NMc2: 539-541)
Mar. 20-Apr.10, 1920 Paintings by Hayley Lever (NMc2: 542-545)
Apr. 5-24, 1920 Group of Paintings by Felicie Waldo Howell (NMc2: 546)
Apr. 5-24, 1920 Paintings by Maurice Fromke (NMc2: 546-548)
Oct. 18-Nov. 8, 1920 Paintings of the Orient by Hovsep Pushman (NMc2: 550-554)
Oct. 18-Nov. 8, 1920 Group of Paintings by Ben Foster, Robert Henri, Hayley Lever, Gardner Symons (NMc2: 555-558)
Nov. 9-29, 1920 Paintings by Frank W. Benson and Willard L. Metcalf (NMc2: 559-562)
Nov. 30-Dec. 31, 1920 Fourth Exhibition of Intimate Paintings (NMc2: 564-570)
Jan. 3-17, 1921 Recent Landscapes by Chauncey F. Ryder (NMc2: 573-576)
Jan. 3-17, 1921 Old Salem Doorways Painted Last Summer by Felicie Waldo Howell (NMc2: 577-581)
Jan. 18-Feb. 7, 1921 Thirty Paintings by Thirty Artists (NMc2: 583-588)
Feb. 9-28, 1921 An American Summer in Watercolors by F. Luis Mora (NMc2: 596-599)
Feb. 9-28, 1921 The East Side in Sculpture by Abastenia St. L. Eberle (NMc2: 600)
Feb. 9-28, 1921 Recent Paintings by Emil Carlsen (Br14: 623; NMc2: 589-594)
Mar. 1-21, 1921 Connecticut Landscapes by Charles H. Davis (NMc2: 603-606)
Mar. 1-21, 1921 Paintings of Cornwall and Elsewhere by W. Elmer Schofield (NMc2: 607-610)
Mar. 1-21, 1921 Annual Exhibition, Society of Animal Painters and Sculptors (NMc2: 611-616
Mar. 22-Apr. 11, 1921 Paintings by F. C. Frieseke and Albert L. Groll (NMc2: 621-624)
Mar. 22-Apr. 11, 1921 Paintings by Jonas Lie (NMc2: 617-620)
Mar. 22-Apr. 11, 1921 Portraits and Landscapes by Gladys Thayer (NMc2: 625-628)
Apr. 12-May 7, 1921 Loan Exhibition of Paintings by J. Francis Murphy, 1853-1921 (NMc2: 629-637)
Oct. 11-30, 1921 Opening Exhibition, Season of 1921-1922: Group of Selected Paintings (NMc2: 640-641)
Nov. 1-19, 1921 West Indian Marines by Frederick J. Waugh (NMc2: 642-645)
Nov. 21-Dec. 12, 1921 Fifth Exhibition of Intimate Paintings (NMc2: 646-655)
Dec. 13-Jan. 2, 1922 Paintings of Glacier National Park by Charles Warren Eaton (NMc2: 660, 664-666)
Dec. 13-Jan. 2, 1922 Oils, Pastels, and Watercolors by George Alfred Williams (NMc2: 660-663)
Scrapbook 8, January 1922-March 1923
Date Exhibition
Jan. 3-23, 1922 Paintings of South America by E. W. Deming (NMc2: 669-670)
Jan. 3-23, 1922 New England Streets by Felicie Waldo Howell (NMc2: 671-674)
Jan. 3-23, 1922 California Landscapes by F. Ballard Williams (NMc2: 677-680)
Jan. 24-Feb. 13, 1922 Paintings by Elliot Torrey (NMc2: 681-684)
Jan. 24-Feb. 20, 1922 Thirty Paintings by Thirty Artists (NMc2: 685-692)
Feb. 14-Mar. 6, 1922 Third Annual Exhibition, Society of Animal Painters and Sculptors (NMc2: 694-698)
Mar. 7-27, 1922 Paintings by Edmund Greacen (NMc2: 704-707)
Mar. 7-27, 1922 Paintings by Gardner Symons (NMc2: 700-705)
Mar. 28-Apr. 17, 1922 Paintings by Charles H. Davis (NMc2: 707-717)
Apr. 27-May 20, 1922 Paintings by Frederick C. Frieseke Hayley Lever and Malcolm Parcell (NMc2: 721-726)
Apr. 27-May 20, 1922 Paintings by Malcolm Parcell (NMc2: 722)
Oct. 31-Nov. 20, 1922 Paintings by Alice Worthington Ball (NMc2: 731-735)
Oct. 31-Nov. 20, 1922 Recent Paintings and Figure Compositions by Charles W. Hawthorne (NMc2: 731-735)
Nov. 21-Dec. 11, 1922 Sixth Exhibition of Intimate Paintings (NMc2: 738-747)
Nov. 21-Dec. 11, 1922 George Wharton Edwards (NMc2: 748-749)
Dec. 12-30, 1922 Imaginitive Landscapes by W. G. Krieghoff (NMc2: 751-752)
Dec. 12-30, 1922 Watercolors of New York by Joseph Pennell (NMc2: 751, 753-755)
Jan. 2-22, 1923 Paintings and Studies by Orland Campbell (NMc2: 758-761)
Jan. 2-22, 1923 Recent Landscapes by Daniel Garber (NMc2: 758, 762-764)
Jan. 2-22, 1923 Decorative Paintings by Spencer Nichols (NMc2: 765, 769)
Jan. 2-22, 1923 Figure Compositions by Ivan G. Olinsky (NMc2: 765-768)
Jan. 23-Feb. 12, 1923 The Canadian Rockies in Paintings by Belmore Browne (NMc2: 772, 778)
Jan. 23-Feb. 12, 1923 Thirty Paintings by Thirty Artists (NMc2: 772-777)
Jan. 23-Feb. 12, 1923 Decorative Panels by Felicie Waldo Howell (NMc2: 778-782)
Feb. 13-Mar. 5, 1923 Paintings by Ruth A. Anderson and Elizabeth C. Spencer (NMc2: 783, 788-790)
Feb. 13-Mar. 5, 1923 Landscapes by Chauncey F. Ryder (NMc2: 783-786)
Feb. 13-Mar. 5, 1923 Paintings of the West by Maynard Dixon (NMc2: 783, 787)
Mar. 6-26, 1923 Recent Paintings by Emil Carlsen (NMc2: 792-794)
Mar. 12-31, 1923 Watercolors by J. Olaf Olson (NMc2: 795-796)
Scrapbook 9, March 1923-December 1924
Date Exhibition
Mar. 27-Apr. 16, 1923 Paintings by John J. Enneking (NMc3: 1-4)
Apr. 17-May7, 1923 Paintings by Maurice Braun (NMc3: 5-8)
Apr. 17-May 7, 1923 Recent Paintings by Catharine Wharton Morris (NMc3: 5, 9)
Oct. 9-29, 1923 Opening Exhibition, Season 1923-1924 (NMc3: 17-22)
Oct. 30-Nov. 19, 1923 Paintings by Emil Carlsen, Theodore Robsinson, J. Alden Weir (NMc3: 24-27)
Nov. 20-Dec. 10, 1923 Seventh Exhibition of Intimate Paintings (NMc3: 30-35)
Nov. 20-Dec. 11, 1923 South American Sketches by Rachel Hartley (NMc3: 37-42)
Dec. 11-31, 1923 Scenes about Provincetown by Charles W. Hawthorne; Flowers by Marion C. Hawthorne (NMc3: 37, 43)
Dec. 11-31, 1923 Recent Paintings by Douglas Parshall (NMc3: 44)
Dec. 1923 Collection of Paintings from the Macbeth Gallery, Halaby Galleries, Dallas (NMc3: 47-54)
Jan. 2-21, 1924 Paintings by Robert Henri and Grace Ravlin (NMc3: 56-57)
Feb. 7-25, 1924 Thirty Paintings by Thirty Artists (NMc3: 62-68)
Feb. 26-Mar. 17, 1924 Paintings by Victor Higgins (NMc3: 68, 72-74)
Feb. 26-Mar. 17, 1924 Paintings by Frank Duveneck (NMc3: 68-69)
Mar. 18-Apr. 7, 1924 Paintings from Tusayan by Maynard Dixon (NMc3: 76-79)
Apr. 8-28, 1924 Paintings of the Orient by Hovsep Pushman (NMc3: 80-82)
Apr. 8-28, 1924 The Canadian Rockies in Paintings by Belmore Browne (NMc3: 80, 84)
Sept. 23-Oct. 6, 1924 Paintings of the French West Indies by Christiana Moron (NMc3: 86-87)
Oct. 7-27, 1924 Selected Group of Paintings by Thirty American Artists (NMc3: 86, 88)
Nov. 4-17, 1924 Recent Paintings by Chauncey F. Ryder (NMc3: 90-91)
Nov. 18-Dec. 8, 1924 A Group of Paintings by Frederick C. Frieseke (NMc3: 92-93)
Dec. 9-29, 1924 Retrospective Exhibition of Paintings by Louis Comfort Tiffany (NMc3: 95-97)
Scrapbook 10, January 1925-November 1927
Date Exhibition
Dec. 30-Jan. 19, 1925 Montauk by Childe Hassam (NMc3: 104-112)
Jan. 20-Feb. 9, 1925 George Inness Centennial Exhibition, 1825-1894 (NMc3: 117-123)
Feb. 10-Mar. 2, 1925 Water Colors of Egypt and Jerusalem by Taber Sears (NMc3: 126, 129-130)
Feb. 10-Mar.2, 1925 The New England Year in Paintings by Charles H. Davis (NMc3: 126-128)
Mar. 3-23, 1925 Paintings by E. W. Redfield (NMc3: 131-133)
Mar. 24-Apr. 13, 1925 Paintings by Daniel Garber (NMc3: 135-138)
Apr. 14-May 4, 1925 Recent Paintings by Robert Henri (NMc3: 140-143)
Apr. 14-May 4, 1925 C. W. Hawthorne: Watercolors of Bermuda (NMc3: 139)
Oct. 13-26, 1925 Collection of American Masters Loaned for Exhibition (NMc3: 152-154)
Oct. 27-Nov. 16, 1925 Memorial Exhibition of Paintings by the Late William Sartain (NMc3: 155-158)
Nov. 7-23, 1925 Paintings by Contemporary American Artists Loaned by the Macbeth Galleries, New York, Engaged by the Muncie Art Students?? League, Muncie, Indiana (NMc3: 147-148)
Nov. 17-Dec. 7, 1925 Paintings by DeWitt and Douglass Parshall (NMc3: 159-162)
Dec. 4-31, 1925 Easel Paintings by American Artists, Loaned by Macbeth Galleries to the Springfield Art Association (NMc3: 205, 207)
Dec. 8-Jan. 4, 1926 Watercolors by Distinguished American Artists (NMc3: 163-166)
Jan. 5-25, 1926 Recent American Portraits (NMc3: 168, 172-173)
Jan. 5-18, 1926 American Society of Miniature Painters, 27th Annual Exhibition (NMc3: 168-171)
Jan. 26-Feb. 15, 1926 Paintings by Jonas Lie (NMc3: 176-179)
Jan. 26-Feb. 15, 1926 First Exhibition of Paintings by John Huffington (NMc3: 176, 180-181)
Feb. 7-Mar. 17, 1926 Exhibition of Oil Paintings by American Artists Lent by the Macbeth Galleries to the Utica Public Library Art Gallery (NMc3: 205-206)
Feb. 16-Mar. 8, 1926 New Paintings by Charles W. Hawthorne (NMc3: 186-189)
Feb. 16-Mar. 8, 1926 Chauncey F. Ryder (NMc3: 184)
Feb. 16-Mar. 8, 1926 Sculpture by Gleb Derujinsky (NMc3: 186-189)
Mar. 9-29, 1926 Modern Landscapes by Guy Wiggins (NMc3: 191-194)
Mar. 9-29, 1926 Etchings and Drawings by Emil Fuchs (NMc3: 191, 195-197)
Mar. 30-Apr. 19, 1926 The Affairs of Anatol by Robert Reid (NMc3: 198-201)
Apr. 20-May 3, 1926 Pastels Done in Spain by A. Sheldon Pennoyer (NMc3: 202)
June 1-25, 1926 Pictures Selected from the Brooklyn Museum Exhibition of the National Association of Women Painters and Sculptors (NMc3: 204)
Summer, 1926 Summer Exhibition (NMc3: 199-201)
Oct. 11-18, 1926 Paintings Selected by Louis Bliss Gillet (NMc3: 210-212)
Oct. 19-Nov. 8, 1926 Paintings by Stanley M. Woodward (Br14: 671; NMc3: 213-214)
Nov. 9-22, 1926 Ernest Haskell, 1876-1925, Memorial Exhibition (NMc3: 215-222)
Nov. 23-Dec. 6, 1926 Porto Rico and St. Thomas: Exhibition of Paintings by Rachel Hartley (NMc3: 226-229)
Nov. 23-Dec. 6, 1926 Recent Landscapes and Marines by Jay H. Connaway (NMc3: 226, 230)
Dec. 1926 Watercolors and Etchings by American Artists (NMc3: 231-233)
Dec. 28-Jan. 10, 1927 Recent Paintings by a Group of Mystic, Conn., Artists (NMc3: 235-238)
Jan. 11-31, 1927 Thirty Paintings by Thirty Artists (NMc3: 239-244)
Jan. 18-31, 1927 Watercolors by John Lavalle of Boston (NMc3: 253-255)
Jan. 22-Feb. 7, 1927 Crapo Gallery Opening Exhibition: Thirty Paintings by Thirty Artists assembled by Macbeth Gallery at Swain School, New Bedford, Mass. (NMc3: 245-249)
Feb. 1-14, 1927 Recent Paintings by Frank W. Benson (NMc3: 259-262)
Feb. 2-14, 1927 American Society of Miniature Painters, 28th Annual Exhibition (NMc3: 253, 256-258)
Feb. 8-26, 1927 Works by American Artists Selected by the Associated Dealers in American Paintings, Inc. at Anderson Galleries (Macbeth Gallery one of nine participants (NMc3: 263, 265-271)
Feb. 15-28, 1927 New Paintings by Chauncey F. Ryder (NMc3: 278-281)
Mar. 1-14, 1927 Watercolors by Aiden L. Ripley (NMc3: 282, 286)
Mar. 1-14, 1927 Paintings by a Group of Members of the Guild of Boston Artists (NMc3: 282-285)
Mar. 15-28, 1927 Paintings by Malcolm Parcell (NMc3: 287-290)
Mar. 15-28, 1927 Recent Pastels of Chartres by Carl Schmidt (NMc3: 287)
Mar. 29-Apr. 18, 1927 Thirty-fifty Anniversary Exhibition, Retrospect and Prospective (NMc3: 291-294)
Apr. 19-May 9, 1927 Frank A. Brown, Watercolors (NMc3: 296, 302-303)
Aug. 22-Sept. 5, 1927 American Art Exhibition arranged for Eastern Long Island by the Macbeth Gallery at Southampton, NY (NMc3: 297-301)
Oct. 18-29, 1927 American Art Exhibition, Art League of Fort Worth, Assembeled by the Macbeth Gallery (NMc3: 304, 306-311)
Oct. 18-31, 1927 Etchings by Walter Raymond Duff (NMc3: 313-315)
Oct. 18-31, 1927 Paintings by Max Bohm (NMc3: 313-315)
Nov. 1-14, 1927 Yankee Whalers by Clifford W. Ashley (NMc3: 316-317)
Scrapbook 11, November 1927-June 1930
Date Exhibition
Nov. 15-28, 1927 Paintings of Mallorca by Bernhard Gutmann (NMc3: 319-320)
Nov. 15-28, 1927 Paintings of Flowers by Carle J. Blenner (NMc3: 319, 321)
Nov. 29-Dec. 12, 1927 The Bathers, Paintings by William S. Horton (NMc3: 322-325)
Nov. 29-Dec. 12, 1927 Sidewalks of New York, Chalk Drawings by H. Devitt Welsh (NMc3: 326-327)
Dec. 13-31, 1927 Joint Exhibition of Paintings by Daniel Garber and Stanley Woodward (NMc3: 328)
Jan. 3-16, 1928 Portrait Drawings by Edith Leslie Emmet (NMc3: 329, 331)
Jan. 3-23, 1928 Recent Paintings by Jonas Lie (NMc3: 329-330)
Jan. 24-Feb. 13, 1928 Watercolors by John Lavalle (NMc3: 332-334)
Jan. 24-Feb. 13, 1928 Walter Ufer: Pictures from Taos (NMc3: 332, 334)
Jan. 24-Feb. 6, 1928 American Society of Miniature Painters, 29th Annual Exhibition (NMc3: 337-340)
Feb. 7-21, 1928 Small Pictures of Mountain and Sea by Jay Connaway (NMc3: 342)
Feb. 14-27, 1928 The Canadian Rockies by Belmore Brown (NMc3: 342-343)
Feb. 14-27, 1928 Sculpture by Gleb Derujinsky (NMc3: 342-344)
Feb. 21-Mar. 5, 1928 Watercolors of Venice, Spain and Brittany by Frank A. Brown (NMc3: 351-356)
Feb. 21-Mar. 10, 1928 Works by American Artists Selected by the Associated Dealers in American Paintings, Inc., at Anderson Galleries; Macbeth Gallery one of sixteen participants (NMc3: 346-352)
Feb. 25-Mar. 17, 1928 The Macbeth-Milch Circuit Exhibition of Contemporary American Paintings at Grand Rapids Art Gallery (NMc3: 385-387)
Feb. 28-Mar. 12, 1928 Paintings by Frank L. Schenk, 1856-1927 (NMc3: 357-358)
Feb. 28-Mar. 19, 1928 Thirty Paintings by Thirty Artists (NMc3: 357, 359-363)
Mar. 20-Apr. 2, 1928 Lanscapes of Italy by A. Sheldon Pennoyer (NMc3: 366, 368)
Mar. 20-Apr. 9, 1928 Recent Landscapes, Switzerland and Other Subjects by Carl Lawless (NMc3: 366-367)
Apr. 2-15, 1928 Water Colors by Earl Winslow (NMc3: 355)
Apr. 10-30, 1928 St. Ives by Hayley Lever (NMc3: 369)
Apr. 29-May 20, 1928 The Macbeth-Milch Circuit Exhibition of Contemporary American Paintings at the University of Wyoming (NMc3: 385-386)
Spring, 1928 American Painting for Home Decoration (NMc3: 370-377)
Oct. 16-29, 1928 The Canadian Rockies in Watercolors by J. Olaf Olson (NMc3: 389-392)
Nov. 7-24, 1928 Etchings by Sears Gallagher (NMc3: 393)
Nov. 13-26, 1928 Sand Dunes and Flowers by Frederick Lowell (NMc3: 393-394)
Nov. 26-Dec. 17, 1928 Etchings by Carlton T. Chapman (NMc3: 395)
Nov. 27-Dec. 10, 1928 Portraits by Ernest L. Ipsen (NMc3: 396-397)
Dec. 4-31, 1928 Etchings by Margery A. Ryerson (NMc3: 395)
Dec. 11-24, 1928 Landscapes in Watercolor and Gouache by H. Anthony Dyer and Character Studies in Watercolor and Pastel by Nancy Dyer (NMc3: 398-400)
Jan. 2-14, 1929 Figures and Landscapes by the Late J. Alden Weir, 1852-1929 (NMc3: 401-402)
Jan. 15-28, 1929 Paintings by H. Dudley Murphy; Watercolors by Nellie Littlehale Murphy (NMc3: 404-405)
Jan. 15-28, 1929 Portraits by William James (NMc3: 406-407)
Feb. 4-18, 1929 Twenty-five Etchings by Harold Denison (NMc3: 410, 416-417)
Feb. 5-18, 1929 Paintings by Emil Carlsen and Dines Carlsen (NMc3: 408-409)
Feb. 19-Mar. 4, 1929 Thirty Paintings by Thirty Artists (NMc3: 410-415)
Mar. 5-18, 1929 Marine Paintings by Stanley W. Woodward (NMc3: 419-423)
Mar. 19-Apr. 1, 1929 Watercolors by Frederick C. Frieseke (NMc3: 424-425)
Mar. 19-Apr. 1, 1929 Pastels of Louisiana by Will H. Stevens (NMc3: 424)
Apr. 1929 Paintings by Childe Hassam (NMc3: 433-438)
Apr. 2-15, 1929 Paintings by Arthur Meltzer (NMc3: 431)
Apr. 2-15, 1929 Watercolors by Earle B. Winslow (NMc3: 431)
June, 1929 Old Mill Afternoon by Childe Hassam, Ainslie Galleries, Inc., Detroit in collaboration with Macbeth Gallery (NMc3: 465-467)
Oct. 1-14, 1929 Portraits in Oil and Pastel by Paul Swan (NMc3: 472-473)
Oct. 15-28, 1929 Exhibitions from the Summer Colonies: No. 1, Lyme (NMc3: 476-477)
Oct. 19-29, 1929 Milch-Macbeth Exhibition of Prints and Paintings by American Artists at the High Museum under the auspices of the Atlanta Art Association (NMc3: 462)
Oct. 20-Nov. 11, 1929 Memorial Exhibition of Paintings by John Huffington (NMc3: 476-479)
Nov. 12-25, 1929 Exhibition from the Summer colonies: No. 2, Selections from the North Shore Arts Association of Gloucester (NMc3: 480-481)
Nov. 26-Dec. 3, 1929 Recent Landscapes by Charles H. Davis (NMc3: 482-483)
Dec. 10-Dec. 23, 1929 Watercolors by J. Olaf Olson (NMc3: 484-486)
Dec. 24-Jan. 6, 1930 Exhibitions from the Summer Colonies: No. 3, Mystic (NMc3: 487-488)
Jan. 7-20, 1930 Paintings of Wyoming Days and Nights by Ogden N. Pleissner (NMc3: 490, 492)
Jan. 21-Feb. 3, 1930 Landscapes by Aldro T. Hibbard (NMc3: 490-491)
Feb. 4-17, 1930 Thirty Paintings by Thirty Artists (NMc3: 493-498)
Feb. 4-18, 1930 Monotypes in Black and White by Seth Hoffman (NMc3: 500-502)
Feb. 18-Mar. 3, 1930 Decorative Pastels by Wilbur A. Reaser (NMc3: 503-504)
Feb. 18-Mar. 3, 1930 Landscapes by John F. Carlson (NMc3: 503, 505
Mar. 4-17, 1930 Art of the Cartoon by Clare A. Briggs (NMc3: 507)
Mar. 4-17, 1930 Watercolors by Gladys Brannigan (NMc3: 507)
Mar. 18-31, 1930 Landscapes by Chauncey F. Ryder (NMc3: 508-509)
Apr. 1-14, 1930 Landscapes by Harry Leith-Ross (NMc3: 510-511)
Apr. 15-29, 1930 The Soviet Union as Seen by Eliot O??Hara (NMc3: 512-513)
Spring 1930 Spring/Summer Exhibition (NMc3: 514-516)
Scrapbook 12, September 1930-December 1932
Date Exhibition
Oct. 1930 Opening Exhibition, 1930-1931 Season (NMc3: 517-519)
Oct. 14-Nov. 4, 1930 Etchings by Thomas Handforth (NMc3: 523-524)
Nov. 1930 Paintings of Museum Importance (NMc3: 521)
Nov. 4-25, 1930 Monotypes in Black and White by Seth Hoffman (NMc3: 522, 524
Dec. 1930 Paintings by Young Americans (NMc3: 525)
Dec. 1930 Etchings and Lithographs by Edward Haskell (NMc3: 526-527)
Jan. 6-31, 1931 Brittany and Other Recent Paintings by Jonas Lie (NMc3: 528-531)
Feb. 2-8, 1931 Group Exhibition of Important Paintings (NMc3: 535)
Feb. 9-21, 1931 Brackman (NMc3: 536)
Feb. 24-Mar. 7, 1931 Paintings by Paul Dougherty and Mahonri Young (NMc3: 539)
Mar. 9-28, 1931 Recent Paintings by Daniel Garber (NMc3: 540)
Mar. 30-Apr. 11, 1931 Brittany Subjects by Jay Connaway, Landscapes by Arthur Meltzer, Pastel Impressions by J. H. Guest (NMc3: 545-549)
Apr. 13-May 2, 1931 Paintings and Drawings by Abbot H. Thayer (NMc3: 545-549)
May, 1931 Selected Paintings and Etchings by American Artists (NMc3: 552-553)
Oct. 1931 October Show (NMc3: 355)
Oct. 1931 October Watercolor Exhibition (NMc3: 556)
Nov. 4-30, 1931 Fifteen New Paintings from the Artists Studios (NMc3: 558-559)
Nov. 11-Dec. 31, 1931 Lithographs by Stow Wengenroth (NMc3: 560-566)
Dec. 1-19, 1931 Small Paintings by Ivan Olinsky and Cecil Chichester (NMc3: 562-563)
Dec. 8-31, 1931 Wood Engravings by Thomas Nason (NMc3: 564)
Dec. 21-Jan. 9, 1932 Maine Coast Towns by C. K. Chatterton (NMc3: 565-566)
Jan. 11-23, 1932 Landscapes, Figures, Still Life Subjects Painted in Vermont by Herbert Meyer (NMc3: 564)
Jan. 11-23, 1932 Paintings by Lily Cushing (NMc3: 569, 571)
Jan. 25-Feb. 13, 1932 Hudson River School (NMc3: 573-576)
Feb. 15-27, 1932 Paintings by James Chapin (NMc3: 589)
Feb. 15-Mar. 1, 1932 Monotypes in Black and White by Seth Hoffman (NMc3: 590-591)
Feb. 29-Mar. 10, 1932 Sanford Ross: 16 Wash Drawings of 16 New Jersey Landmarks (NMc3: 598-599)
Feb. 29-Mar. 12, 1932 George Fuller, 1822-1844 (NMc3: 593-596)
Mar. 14-26, 1932 Winter Landscapes and Other Subjects by F. C. Frieseke (NMc3: 600-601)
Mar. 28-Apr. 9, 1932 Recent Paintings by Jonas Lie (NMc3: 603)
Apr. 11-30, 1932 Forty Years of American Art (NMc3: 605-610)
May 2-14, 1932 Paintings by a Group of Younger Artists (NMc3: 616-618)
June 1932 June Exhibition (NMc3: 619)
Sept. 26-Oct. 15, 1932 Paintings from the Summer Colonies (NMc3: 621-622)
Oct. 17-Nov. 7, 1932 Special Sale Exhibition (NMc3: 626-628)
Oct. 17-Nov. 7, 1932 Etchings and Lithographs by Mons Breidvik (NMc3: 626-627)
Nov. 9-26, 1932 Paintings by Max Bohm, Eugene Higgins, Jerome Myers, John Noble (NMc3: 630)
Nov. 14-Dec. 5, 1932 Lithographs by Stow Wengenroth (NMc3: 630)
Nov. 29-Dec. 12, 1932 Vermont Watercolors by Henry Holt (NMc3: 632-633)
Dec. 6-19, 1932 Lights of New York by Felicie Waldo Howell (NMc3: 634-635)
Dec. 14-Jan. 3, 1933 Paintings by Robert Strong Woodward (NMc3: 636)
Scrapbook 13, 1932
Scrapbook of 40th Anniversary of Macbeth Gallery, 1932.
Scrapbook 14, 1930-1934
Date Exhibition
Jan. 1-29, 1933 Forty Years of American Painting assembled by the Macbeth Gallery at Montclair Art Museum (NMc4: 263-268)
July 9-25, 1933 American Landscapes assembled by the Macbeth Gallery at Four Fountains, Southampton, NY (NMc4: 290-295)
Scrapbook 15, January 1933-February 1935
Date Exhibition
Jan. 1933 Watercolors Made by Americans, Assembled by the College Art Association (NMc3: 639-641)
Jan. 3-16, 1933 Drawings by J. Louis Lundean (NMc3: 643)
Jan. 17-30, 1933 Paintings of Flowers by C. G. Nelson (NMc3: 644)
Jan. 31-Feb. 13, 1933 Intimate Paintings (NMc3: 645)
Feb. 21-Mar. 6, 1933 Group Exhibition (NMc3: 646)
Mar. 1933 Paintings and Etchings by Living American Artists (NMc3: 647-648)
Mar. 7-20, 1933 Paintings by Robert Henri (NMc3: 649)
Mar. 21-Apr. 3, 1933 Watercolors by Sanford Ross (NMc3: 652)
Mar. 21-Apr. 10, 1933 Brackman (NMc3: 652-653)
Apr. 4-17, 1933 Opportunity Exhibition (NMc3: 661)
Apr. 4-18, 1933 Drawings by Adolf Dehn (NMc3: 661)
Apr. 11-24, 1933 The Sea at Monhegan by Jay Connaway (NMc3: 662)
Apr. 18-May 1, 1933 Watercolor Exhibition (NMc3: 663)
Apr. 25-May 8, 1933 Paintings by A. T. Hibbard, Hayley Lever and Ivan G. Olinsky (NMc3: 664)
May 2-22, 1933 Mono-Etchings by Bernard Sanders (NMc3: 664)
May 9-29, 1933 Child Portraits by Margery Ryerson (NMc3: 669)
May 16-29, 1933 Exhibition of Figures and Still Lifes, Macbeth Gallery Extension (NMc3: 669)
June 1933 American Art Past and Present (NMc3: 671)
Oct. 17-30, 1933 Paintings and Watercolors by a Group of American Artists Under 35 (NMc3: 672)
Oct. 31-Nov. 13, 1933 Drawings by Robert Henri (NMc3: 673)
Oct.-Nov. 1933 Mexico as Seen by American Printmakers (NMc3: 674)
Nov. 4-27, 1933 Brackman Portraits: Figures in Pastel (NMc3: 675, 678)
Nov. 4-27, 1933 American Sport and Other Subjects by Percy Crosby (NMc3: 675-677)
Nov. 28-Dec. 11, 1933 Paintings by Ogden M. Pleissner (NMc3: 684, 686)
Nov. 28-Dec. 11, 1933 Figures and Fantacies by Ralph Rowntree (NMc3: 684-685)
Nov. 28-Dec. 11, 1933 Paintings by Horace Day (NMc3: 681)
Nov. 28-Dec. 11, 1933 Drawings by Jerome Myers (NMc3: 682-683)
Dec. 12-23, 1933 Paintings by Janet Scudder (NMc3: 687)
Dec. 12-23, 1933 The New York Scene in Watercolor by Hamilton A. Wolf (NMc3: 688-689)
Dec. 26-Jan. 8, 1934 Group Exhibition, Members of the Louis Comfort Tiffany Foundation (NMc3: 692)
Jan. 9-27, 1934 Paintings by Herbert Meyer (NMc3: 692)
Jan. 24-Feb. 6, 1934 Oils, Watercolors, Drawings, Etchings by Harrison Cady (NMc3: 696-697)
Jan. 30-Feb. 19, 1934 Paintings and Drawings by Lintott (NMc3: 699-700)
Feb. 20-Mar. 12, 1934 Paintings by C. K. Chatterton (NMc3: 703-704)
Feb. 27-Mar. 12, 1934 Golinkin (NMc3: 707-708)
Mar. 6-20, 1934 Drawings by Meyer Bernstein (NMc3: 709)
Mar. 13-36, 1934 Paintings by Jonas Lie (NMc3: 710)
Mar. 20-Apr. 2, 1934 Watercolors of South America by Eliot O'Hara (NMc3: 712)
Mar. 27-Apr. 16, 1934 Memorial Exhibition, Paintings by Charles H. Davis, 1856-1933 (NMc3: 715-722)
Apr. 3-16, 1934 Drawings by Hetty Beatty, Sculptor (NMc3: 726)
Apr. 10-23, 1934 Oils and Watercolors by Gertrude Schweitzer (NMc3: 726)
Apr. 17-May 1, 1934 Monhegan Marines by Jan Connaway (NMc3: 727)
May 1-14, 1934 Watercolors and Pastels by H. Amaird Oberteuffer and Karl Oberteuffer (NMc3: 728)
May 1-21, 1934 Review of the Season (NMc3: 729)
May 7-14, 1934 Paintings by John C. E. Taylor, William Luther King, Stuyvesant van Veen (NMc3: 730)
May 1934? Third Exhibition and Sale of American Paintings at $100 (NMc3: 731)
June 4-15, 1934 Our Glorious Navy: Paintings by Arthur Beaumont, Lieut. U.S.N.R. (NMc3: 732-733)
Oct. 1-15, 1934 Opening Exhibition, Season of 1934-1935, Paintings by Nelson A. Moore, 1924-1902 (NMc3: 735-736)
Oct. 16-30, 1934 Collectors Examples of American Painting (NMc3: 739-740)
Nov. 7-19, 1934 Greenland and Other Subjects by Rockwell Kent (NMc3: 742-743)
Nov. 20-Dec. 3, 1934 Southern New Mexico: Drawings and Lithographs by Peter Hurd (NMc3: 748-749)
Nov. 20-Dec. 11, 1934 Brackman (NMc3: 742-743)
Dec. 4-31, 1934 Lithographs and Drawings of Stow Wengenroth (NMc3: 750)
Dec. 11-31, 1934 Robert Hallowell, Mostly Portraits (NMc3: 751-752)
Jan. 2-14, 1935 Leopold Seyffert, Subjects from Guatemala and Flowers (NMc3: 754-755)
Jan. 22-Feb. 4, 1935 Group of Paintings by Younger Artists (NMc3: 756)